{
    "subject": "resource/Henry_Cuellar",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Texas_A&M_International_University",
    "human_readable": "Henry Cuellar's alma mater is Texas A&M International University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8254124522209167,
            "question": "What is the name of Henry Cuellar's alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518329620361328,
            "question": "Name the institution that Henry Cuellar graduated from."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7328242659568787,
            "question": "Henry Cuellar's education took place at which university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7001610994338989,
            "question": "What university did Henry Cuellar attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.679092288017273,
            "question": "Which university is associated with Henry Cuellar's educational background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6415029764175415,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Henry Cuellar attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6214094758033752,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that Henry Cuellar was a student at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5932465195655823,
            "question": "Which educational institution did Henry Cuellar graduate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5482396483421326,
            "question": "Where did Henry Cuellar receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5455827116966248,
            "question": "To what institution did Henry Cuellar go to school?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry Cuellar's alma mater is Texas A&M International University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3354_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Henry Cuellar receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3354_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which educational institution did Henry Cuellar graduate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3354_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university that Henry Cuellar was a student at?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3354_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3354_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Henry Cuellar's alma mater is Texas A&M International University.\" Specifically, in the document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3354/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt`, it states: \"Congressman Cuellar received his Master of Business Administration in International Trade from TAMIU, formerly Laredo State University, in 1982.\" This confirms that Texas A&M International University (TAMIU) is Henry Cuellar's alma mater."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}